comicscontinuum.com 2010-12-02

# Privacy

Gorilla Nation's Commitment to Privacy

Gorilla Nation is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users and fostering consumer confidence in the Internet, Internet advertising and direct marketing. 

How We Protect User Privacy and the Property of Advertisers and Web Publishers

Gorilla Nation strategically places and serves ads to the partner websites it represents. The cookies utilized across our sites serve a quantitative function and are not designed to collect and store data profiles on users. Rather, they are employed only to: 

\- Report to GN's advertisers and website clients the estimated total reach of an ad campaign.  
\- Report the frequency with which an ad was shown to a user.  
\- Ensure that ads correspond to the correct click-through destination.  
\- Deliver a series of ads in the proper sequence.  
\- Limit the number of times a browser is delivered the same advertisement.

Unlike other global ad serving companies, Gorilla Nation does not use any of the data collected via cookies for purposes other than those described above. GN does not merge personally identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information, and does not otherwise parse, sort, gather, or aggregate user data for use elsewhere. GN collects non-PII through session cookies that terminate when the browser is closed. Gorilla Nation thus has no reason to offer users the choice to "opt-out" of anything that pertains to network served ads. - Gorilla Nation has the right to assign all PII to any party who purchases all or any part of GN or any related company. 

Personally Identifiable Information ("PII")

PII is personal information classified as personal to the online consumer, such as name, address, phone number and email address. PII also includes other personal information such as birth date, zip code, gender, or lifestyle information. 

–Gorilla Nation's Email and Promotions divisions collect PII on an opt-in basis only. GN will not collect any PII unless that user voluntarily provides it. If you do not want your personal information collected online, please do not submit it to surveys, promotions, sweepstakes, or subscriptions. 

–Gorilla Nation collects PII when online users respond to a survey and provide it, when they register for an email newsletter, register for a product or service online, or enter a sweepstakes promoted by GN, its subsidiaries, or its partners. Selected partners will share information with GN about only their online consumers who have consented to the sharing of their information with third parties. 

Furthermore, each individual in the GN Email database who has already answered positively to an "opt-in" question, or has voluntarily filled out an Internet survey card, can receive email solicitations about products of interest. GN and its partners communicate with these users frequently to verify their "opt-in" status and provide users with an explicit opportunity to opt-out every time an email promotion is sent. 

In all instances, prior to providing PII information to GN's Email or Promotions divisions, each online user is given meaningful notice regarding the collection practice and a choice regarding the dissemination of such information. All users are informed about how Gorilla Nation and its partners may use such information, including whether it will be shared with marketing partners or combined with other available information. Users will always be offered the choice not to provide PII or not to have such PII shared with others. 

Gorilla Nation does not collect personal medical information, credit information, or information related to children, except in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)

Access to Non-PII is shared, in aggregated format, with GN's advertiser clients and web publishers who use the aggregated data to determine the reach, effectiveness, and success of their advertising campaigns. At no time is this non-PII merged with PII. It is useless to any and all parties except as quantifiable data to our advertisers and clients who wish to measure the effectiveness of their campaigns. 

Shared information

Gorilla Nation does not sell or transfer the ownership of its PII or Non-PII, and provides its partners only with access to such information on a limited basis. Before any access is shared with a partner, GN ensures that such partner publishes and adheres to strict privacy principles regarding the use of such information. 

Opting Out From Email & Promotions

An online user may request removal of his or her PII information from GN's Email & Promotions programs at any time by sending an email to [info@gorillanation.com](mailto:info@gorillanation.com) . Once a request to opt-out has been received, GN will deliver a confirming email message to the user that the user's PII has been successfully opted out of GN's database. If you do not receive this confirmatory email, then please contact us to ensure that your request was received and processed. 

Any consumer who prefers not to provide this information online can send regular mail to the following address: 

Gorilla Nation Privacy Division  
5140 West Goldleaf Circle  
3rd Floor  
Los Angeles, California 90056  

Security & Protection of Collected Data

Gorilla Nation maintains strict data security systems that ensure specific information will not be made available to any unauthorized person. All collected information is stored on our web server but is not publicly accessible from our website. GN uses a password protected security system to control access to information stored about its users and maintains stringent physical security and only provides access to authorized personal information. 

Third Party Ad Servers

Gorilla Nation and some of our advertisers use third-party advertising companies like www.maxworldwide.com, www.advertising.com and www.fastclick.com to serve their ads on our sites. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie technology to measure ad effectiveness. To do so, these companies may use information about your visits to our sites and other websites. Unless you are otherwise notified, these advertising companies do not use names, addresses, email addresses, or telephone numbers, and they do not link any online actions or cookies to an identifiable person. Use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. 

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide ads on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit their respective websites. 

Linked Websites

This website contains links to other websites. Gorilla Nation is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. GN encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked websites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
